smart city's mission is a program by the
government
to develop 100 smart cities in india
to provide citizens with core
infrastructure
decent quality of life clean and
sustainable environment
and smart solutions across different
areas
to implement this scheme the concerned
authorities may face several challenges
like manage and track projects
payments to vendors monitoring of funds
capital requirement for projects manual
transit
and retail payments
manual reconciliation for bank
guarantees
reconciliation issues in tax collection
cash payment in parking projects manual
refund process for tenders
and cumbersome house identification
process
presenting icici bank's smart city
solution suite
our solutions will help to digitize your
existing processes
and ensure efficient management of smart
city requirements
here's what we offer comprehensive
project
and payment management solution
pfms assistance
in bonds issuance pass tag for digital
payments in parking projects
digital bank guarantee repository
comprehensive tax collection solution
[Music]
digital e-tendering and e-auction
solution
qr code for making utility payments
digital house identification
one city one card solution for a
cashless ecosystem
that's not all additional solutions can
be developed
bases smart city requirements
and there's more all the above solutions
provide
multiple benefits like
detailed mis reports as per desired
frequency
for hassle-free reconciliation
customizable as per your requirements
designed on multiple platforms to take
care of your mobility requirements
dedicated relationship management and
call center support
for more information please contact our
relationship manager
or visit the nearest branch or write to
us
at smart city at icici bank dot com